angular-university.io 2018-09-01

# 

    PRIVACY STATEMENT
    
    ----
    
    SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
    
    When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your email address.
    
    Your email will only be used for:
    
     - essential operations related to accessing and using the website: signing up, logging in, resetting the password, receiving email receipts, replying to support requests
    
     - weekly updates with new educational content
    
     - occasional premium offers
    
    When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
    
    We don't share or sell your email or any other of your personal data with any third-party company for commercial purposes.

    SECTION 2 - CONSENT
    
    How do you get my consent?
    
    When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
    
    If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

    How do I withdraw my consent, or request a complete removal of all my personal data?
    
    If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at admin@angular-university.io

    SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE
    
    We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

    SECTION 4 - HOSTING
    
    Our store is hosted on Heroku. They provide us with the online server platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.
    
    Your data is stored in a database hosted by Heroku. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

    Payment:
    
    All your payments are made via Stripe (https://stripe.com), which is a payment gateway provider similar to Paypal. As such we don't keep the details of your credit card under any circumstances.
    
    Only Stripe gets your credit card details, no part of our system gets your full credit card details.

    SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

    In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
    
    However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
    
    For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
    
    In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
    
    As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
    
    Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

    Links
    
    When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

    SECTION 6 - SECURITY
    
    To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
    
    If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

    SECTION 7 - AGE OF CONSENT
    
    By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

    SECTION 8 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
    
    We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
    
    If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

    QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
    
    If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at admin@angular-university.io or by mail at Angular University
    
    [Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]
    
    [Sq Ambiorix 40, Brussels, BRU, 1000, Belgium]
    
    ----
